Alex Buhai

oleksandr.buugay@gmail.com https://github.com/OleksandrBuhai

SUMMARY

Experienced front end developer with a professional background in crafting complex, interactive web projects since 2021. High at cross-browser development, web standards, usability, responsive web development, and application architecture. I enjoy creating products that will benefit people in the future.

EDUCATION

IT-Incubator.io

May 2020 - May 2021 Front-End Developer

NTUU KPI

Aug. 2015 - May 2019 Studied Manufacturing Engineering

IPTKisSUMDU

Konotop, Ukraine College Degree in Manufacturing Technology May 2013 - May 2015

Experience

Front-End Developer Apr 2023 - Jul 2023

KodableRemote

• Developing new user-facing features using React

- Participation in the development of a project for the sale of photo \ video.
- Optimizing components for maximum performance
- Building reusable components

Front-End Developer

Jun 2022 - Feb 2023

Remote

Kyiv, Ukraine

• Development of landing pages;

- Developing features to enhance the user experience
- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Ensuring web design is optimized for smartphones
- Fix Bugs

Berlin Labs KKC

Front-End Developer

May 2019 - Dec 2021

Selfemploy

Mindy Support

Remote

- Development of landing pages;
- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.

Graphic Assistant

Dec 2016 - Jul 2017

Kyiv, Ukraine

- Data Processing for Neural Networks
- Image Processing for Future Use

Projects

$Portfolio \mid React, JavaScript, CSS$

- https://oleksandrbuhai.github.io/Portfolio/
- Working with libraries framer-motion , React styled component, tsparticles

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Lanuages: English, Czech, Ukranian

ProgLanguages: JavaScript, TypeScript HTML/CSS

Frameworks: React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Tailwind CSS, jQuery, Material-UI

Developer Tools: Git, Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ